(Penny:)So, Leonard, how about it?
(Leonard:)Penny, we'd love to help you, but Raj
is going through some stuff right now.
(Leonard:)And besides, he doesn't drink, so...
[WHISPERING INDISTINCTLY]
(Leonard:)Really?
(Sheldon(on phone):)Um...
(Leonard:)Raj is going through some stuff right now
and he'd like to take up drinking.
(Penny:)Okay, here you go, Leonard.
One Tequila Sunrise.
(Leonard:)- Thank you.
- Mm-hm.
This drink is an example of how liquids
with different specific gravities...
(Leonard:)...interact in a cylindrical container.
(Leonard:)Thank you.
(Penny:)Okay, Raj, what'll it be?
[WHISPERING INDISTINCTLY]
(Leonard:)Whatever you recommend.
How about a Grasshopper?
I make a mean Grasshopper.
(Penny:)Okay? Good, coming up.
- Sheldon, what are you gonna have?
- I'll have a Diet Coke.
Okay, can you please order a cocktail?
I need to practice mixing drinks.
(Sheldon:)Fine. I'll have a virgin Cuba Libre.